// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q023: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'There are three employees ------ for promotion to accounting manager, and they are scheduled to be interviewed by the accounting director next week.',
      choices: ['frequent', 'eligible', 'brief', 'dominant'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['eligible'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Whitfield Legal Office has spent the last two months looking for a place to move its offices, but found ------ properties that met its criteria.',
      choices: ['many', 'other', 'plenty of', 'few'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['few'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Barton was asked by her supervisor to submit a ------ of yesterday’s meeting with a business partner.',
      choices: ['summarily', 'summarized', 'summary', 'summarize'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['summary'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'If the plan had been thoroughly reviewed with his colleagues, Mr. Batista would not ------ with such difficulties.',
      choices: ['having faced', 'had been faced', 'have faced', 'have been faced'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['have been faced'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Springford Technologies has developed an ------ method and automated testing system.',
      choices: ['efficiencies', 'efficient', 'efficiently', 'efficiency'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['efficient'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'System problems that have been occurring since last week need to be ------ urgently.',
      choices: ['founded', 'accompanied', 'addressed', 'praised'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['addressed'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'At Amador Bicycle Shop, sales of bicycle parts rose ------ compared to the previous quarter.',
      choices: ['slighter', 'slight', 'slightest', 'slightly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['slightly'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The city plans to host environmental events to ------ awareness of the new resource conservation program.',
      choices: ['raise', 'discard', 'proofread', 'reimburse'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['raise'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'If you are late returning a rental car for any reason, ------ sure to call the office as soon as possible.',
      choices: ['to make', 'make', 'making', 'made'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['make'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'To participate in this weekend’s Adventure Tour, you must be ------ 12 years old.',
      choices: ['above all', 'at least', 'so far', 'at the latest'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['at least'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}